♪The painting is filled with old dreams and the moonlight is scattered♪
♪ اللوحة مليئة بالأحلام القديمة وضوء القمر متناثر ♪
♪I draw a flower when the light is half dim♪
♪ أرسم زهرة عندما يكون الضوء نصف خافت
♪The wind blows through the eyebrows and the insanity remains♪
تهب الرياح عبر الحاجبين ويبقى الجنون ♪
♪One more step and everything will be fine♪
♪ خطوة أخرى وسيكون كل شيء على ما يرام
♪Who says that things are unpredictable? You're still around♪
♪ من قال أن الأشياء لا يمكن التنبؤ بها؟  أنت ما زلت في الجوار ♪
♪The lonely shadows of the past have gone♪
اختفت الظلال الوحيدة للماضي
♪I'll take the hardships and turn them into liquor♪
♪ سآخذ المصاعب وأحولها إلى خمور
♪Old friends will never be forgotten♪
♪ لن يُنسى الأصدقاء القدامى
♪Who says the world has changed? You never left♪
♪ من قال أن العالم قد تغير؟  أنت لم تغادر أبدًا ♪
♪Yesterday's sorrows and joys are long gone♪
ولت منذ فترة طويلة أحزان وأفراح الأمس ♪
♪I hold the light in my hands only to see this love last♪
♪ أحمل الضوء في يدي فقط لأرى هذا الحب أخيرًا
♪A million dreams for me to look back on♪
♪ مليون حلم بالنسبة لي لأنظر إليها مرة أخرى ♪
=Order of the Sommelier= =Episode 2=
= ترتيب الساقي = = الحلقة 2 =
(Underage viewers are advised to watch under parental consent.)
(يُنصح المشاهدين القاصرين بالمشاهدة بموافقة الوالدين).
All demons in this world
كل الشياطين في هذا العالم
are evil.
هم شريرون.
So they must die.
لذلك يجب أن يموتوا.
Are you humans all so paranoid?
هل جميعكم بشر بجنون العظمة؟
I never even hurt
أنا لم أتألم أبدا
a single flower or grass.
زهرة واحدة أو عشب.
Can you be reasonable?
هل يمكن ان تكون عاقلا؟
Cut the nonsense.
قطع الهراء.
Unreasonable.
غير منطقى.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
You kill demons indiscriminately.
أنت تقتل الشياطين بدون تمييز.
Is your Dharma name Fahai?
هل اسم دارما الخاص بك Fahai؟
Where did you come from,
من أين أتيت،
you little loach?
أنت لوش الصغير؟
You are the little loach.
أنت لوش الصغير.
I am a dragon.
أنا تنين.
A true ancient dragon.
تنين قديم حقيقي.
You don't even have a decent dragon's horn
ليس لديك حتى قرن تنين لائق
and you call yourself a true dragon?
وتسمي نفسك تنين حقيقي؟
Show me how you fly.
أرني كيف تطير.
Come on.
تعال.
I think you can fly
أعتقد أنك تستطيع الطيران
about as high
عن ارتفاع
as a grouse.
كاحتجاج.
Don't go too far.
لا تذهب بعيدا.
So what if you are
إذن ماذا لو كنت كذلك
a true dragon?
تنين حقيقي؟
Don't meddle in my business.
لا تتدخل في عملي.
Do you know
هل تعرف
who I am?
من أكون؟
I'm looking for you.
انا ابحث عنك.
The strongest demon hunter, Fu Yu.
أقوى صائد شياطين ، فو يو.
Reincarnation of the Divine Spirit.
تناسخ الروح الإلهية.
A fearsome presence in the demon world.
حضور مخيف في عالم الشياطين.
(The deities are fighting.)
(الآلهة تقاتل).
(I should sneak away.)
(يجب أن أتسلل بعيدًا).
If I get your alchemy,
إذا حصلت على الكيمياء الخاصة بك ،
I'll have the strongest power
سآخذ أقوى قوة
and maybe
و ربما
I'll grow dragon horns
سأزرع قرون التنين
and soar to the top.
وترتفع إلى القمة.
So
لذا
I'm going to kill you
سأقتلك
and get your alchemy.
واحصل على الكيمياء الخاصة بك.
Here's my chance.
ها هي فرصتي.
Go.
يذهب.
(Hedong Village boundary)
(حدود قرية هيدونغ)
Hedong Village?
(حدود قرية Hedong) قرية Hedong؟
What is this place?
ما هذا المكان؟
I'll check it out.
سوف تحقق من ذلك.
We want our river back!
نريد نهرنا مرة أخرى!
(Hedong Village) Hexi Village should pay for it!
(قرية Hedong) يجب على قرية Hexi دفع ثمنها!
Brothers.
الإخوة.
Are we really going to fight them?
هل سنقاتلهم حقًا؟
You don't know.
أنت لا تعرف.
Those bad guys
هؤلاء الأشرار
beat Hu Shen to death.
ضرب هو شين حتى الموت.
How did Hu Shen die?
كيف مات هو شين؟
He was...
كان...
How did he die?
كيف مات؟
Hu Shen is not dead.
هو شين لم يمت.
I'm alive and well.
أنا على قيد الحياة وبصحة جيدة.
So those guys from Hexi Village
إذاً هؤلاء الرجال من قرية هيكسي
didn't kill you.
لم يقتلك.
Yes.
نعم.
So don't start a fight
لذلك لا تبدأ القتال
at every turn.
عند كل منعطف.
Come on.
تعال.
Let's go home for dinner.
دعنا نذهب إلى المنزل لتناول العشاء.
Good thing you're not dead.
شيء جيد أنك لم تمت.
Come with us
تعال معنا
and finish them off.
والقضاء عليهم.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Brother.
أخ.
Look, I'm hurt badly.
انظري ، لقد تأذيت بشدة.
Let's not have this fight.
دعونا لا نخوض هذه المعركة.
Come on.
تعال.
Get them!
احضرهم!
Give it up.
التخلي عنها.
You can't beat me.
لا يمكنك هزامي.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
What did you drink?
ماذا شربت؟
Sober Demon.
رصين شيطان.
What is Sober Demon?
ما هو شيطان الرصين؟
If you want to know,
إذا أردت أن تعرف،
trade your alchemy for it.
استبدل الخيمياء الخاصة بك من أجلها.
Boss, there is something odd
بوس ، هناك شيء غريب
about your liquor.
عن الخمور الخاصة بك.
Why do I feel like
لماذا أشعر
I keep seeing strange things?
ما زلت أرى أشياء غريبة؟
It's not my liquor that's odd.
ليس الخمور الخاص بي هذا غريب.
All the things you see
كل الأشياء التي تراها
are from inside your heart.
من داخل قلبك.
Nonsense.
كلام فارغ.
Who exactly are you?
من انت بالضبط
I am a man
انا رجل
who has been waiting
الذي كان ينتظر
for someone
من أجل أحد ما
who needs Sober Demon.
الذي يحتاج شيطان رصين.
Give me a break.
أعطني إستراحة.
Didn't you just say
ألم تقل فقط
you hadn't concocted the liquor yet?
لم تكن قد طهرت الخمور بعد؟
That's because
ذلك بسبب
the person I was waiting for
الشخص الذي كنت أنتظره
never came.
لم يأت.
Let me have a sip.
اسمحوا لي أن رشفة.
You want to drink Sober Demon?
هل تريد أن تشرب شيطان الرصين؟
What will you trade for it?
ما الذي ستتاجر به؟
My alchemy.
كيمياء بلدي.
Demon hunters
صيادو الشياطين
are deceitful.
خادعون.
I've caught 10,000 demons.
لقد أمسكت 10000 شيطان.
I will give you
سأعطيك
my alchemy.
كيمياء بلدي.
They say you're ruthless
يقولون أنك قاسي
and a man of your word.
ورجل من كلامك.
I believe you won't lie to me.
أعتقد أنك لن تكذب علي.
It's a deal then.
إنها صفقة إذن.
However,
لكن،
you have to promise me one condition.
عليك أن تعدني بشرط واحد.
There are cause and effect
هناك سبب ونتيجة
and there are good and evil demons.
وهناك شياطين صالحة وشر.
Leave the innocent
اترك الأبرياء
little demons alone.
القليل من الشياطين وحدها.
No way.
مستحيل.
How can there be
كيف يمكن أن يكون هناك
harmless monsters in this world?
الوحوش غير المؤذية في هذا العالم؟
Why don't
لماذا لا تفعل
we make a bet?
نراهن؟
Let's bet on the little fox.
دعونا نراهن على الثعلب الصغير.
(Hedong Village)
(قرية هيدونغ) دعنا نراهن على الثعلب الصغير.
The river is our lifeline.
النهر هو شريان حياتنا.
If you try to snatch it from us, we'll fight you!
إذا حاولت انتزاعها منا ، فسنقاتلك!
Is your name written on the river?
هل اسمك مكتوب على النهر؟
Will it answer to you?
هل ستجيب عليك؟
Bah!
باه!
You rogues.
أيها المحتالون.
You're the rogues.
أنتم المحتالون.
Brothers, get them!
أيها الإخوة ، احصل عليهم!
Come on!
تعال!
Beat them.
إهزمهم.
(Hexi Village Boundary) (I don't want to get involved.)
(Hexi Village Boundary) (لا أريد أن أشارك.)
(I'm off.)
(حدود قرية هيكسي)
Humans are strange.
البشر غريبون.
It's not like the river water
إنها ليست مثل مياه النهر
is going to dry up.
سوف يجف.
Why do they have to fight for it?
لماذا عليهم القتال من أجلها؟
This is strange.
هذا غريب.
I just saw
لقد رايت للتو
a kid from Hedong Village
طفل من قرية هيدونغ
sneak by.
التسلل.
Search over there.
ابحث هناك.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Check it out.
تحقق من ذلك.
(A villager of Hexi Village, Zhu Ping)
(قروي من قرية Hexi ، Zhu Ping) تحقق من ذلك.
Thank you for saving me.
شكرا لك لانقاذي.
Otherwise, I might get beaten up again.
وإلا فقد أتعرض للضرب مرة أخرى.
Don't you remember me?
الا تتذكرني
Me?
أنا؟
Well,
حسنًا،
it was in that bush.
كان في تلك الأدغال.
Two people from two villages met
التقى شخصان من قريتين
and fought.
وقاتلوا.
And you whispered to me
وأنت همست لي
that they were going to fight.
أنهم كانوا ذاهبون للقتال.
Did you get
هل أخذت
this cut on your head from then?
هذا قطع على رأسك منذ ذلك الحين؟
Thank you for what you did.
شكرا لك على ما فعلته.
I'm the one who should be thanking you.
أنا من يجب أن أشكرك.
We're even now.
نحن حتى الآن.
I have to go now.
يجب أن أذهب الآن.
It's getting dark.
المكان يزداد ظلام.
Where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب؟
Are you not afraid?
ألا تخافين؟
Afraid?
خائف؟
Compared to you humans...
مقارنة بكم أيها البشر ...
I mean,
أعني،
the brutal people
الشعب الوحشي
in your village
في قريتك
are scarier.
مرعبون.
That's why I escaped.
لهذا هربت.
I don't know what
لا اعرف ماذا
they're fighting about every day.
إنهم يتشاجرون كل يوم.
And your village.
وقريتك.
You can't even finish the river water.
لا يمكنك حتى إنهاء مياه النهر.
Why not share it together?
لماذا لا تشاركها معا؟
What's there to argue about?
ما الذي هناك للجدل حول؟
You are quite interesting.
أنت ممتع للغاية.
Unlike a human being.
على عكس الإنسان.
Is that a compliment?
هل هذا مجاملة؟
My name is Zhu Ping.
اسمي تشو بينغ.
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
My name?
اسمي؟
I...
أنا...
I'm hungry.
أنا جائع.
♪Which door to open so that I can see you again?♪
♪ أي باب يفتح حتى أتمكن من رؤيتك مرة أخرى؟
♪When the world is snowing heavily♪
♪ عندما يتساقط العالم بغزارة
♪I look back and you still look the same♪
♪ أنظر إلى الوراء وما زلت تبدو كما لو كنت
♪I lost my friends and started to wander♪
♪ فقدت أصدقائي وبدأت أتجول ♪
♪Which liquor shall I drink with you?♪
أي خمور أشرب معك؟
♪We'll drink and travel to a certain place♪
سنشرب ونسافر إلى مكان معين
♪The world and the spiritual realm are all connected♪
العالم والعالم الروحي مترابطان جميعًا ♪
♪Remembering the old days♪
تذكر الأيام الخوالي ♪
♪The past is quietly waiting to be unsealed♪
الماضي ينتظر بهدوء أن يُفتح ♪
♪It reminds me of my intent♪
يذكرني بنيتي ♪
♪Why is reality sometimes more like a dream than memories♪
♪ لماذا يكون الواقع أحيانًا أشبه بالحلم أكثر من الذكريات ♪
♪We promised to walk together through the glory♪
وعدنا أن نسير معًا في المجد
♪I once had you to see the whole world together♪
♪ لقد جعلتك ذات مرة ترى العالم كله معًا
(Do not sell alcohol to minors. Underage drinking is not permitted.)
(لا تبيع الكحول للقصر. لا يُسمح بتناول المشروبات الكحولية دون السن القانونية).